<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.6.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2017-12-04T22:11:01+13:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/</id><title type="html">Hai Tran</title><subtitle>The adventures, lessons, and memories of a young Kiwi, making the most of life.  Live. Learn. Grow.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Capture Your Travel Memories</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/travel/travel-memories" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Capture Your Travel Memories" /><published>2017-01-01T15:33:17+13:00</published><updated>2017-01-01T15:33:17+13:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/travel/travel-memories</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/travel/travel-memories">&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“There are so many tiny, beautiful, funny, tragic moments in your life – how are you going to remember them all?”.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Awhile ago I watched a video of a TEDTalk about a person that would record 1 second of video footage everyday as part of a project, collating the footage. They found that these short 1 second clips were able to help them remember what they did that day and also encouraged them to do something interesting with the day, breaking out of the daily pattern of autopilot. I thought this was a great idea because “visualisation is a way to trigger memory” - Cesar Kuriyama.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can watch the video TEDTalk video here:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/7uN4I1wEOXE&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the past, when I have travelled, I found myself immersed in many activites and experiencing a lot. At the end of the trip, I would forget a lot of the small details and only remember the really important parts. Therefore, I decided to take this concept and apply it to holidays that I go on to make travel videos! I will be posting a lot of those travel memories on this page, hopefully you enjoy it.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">“There are so many tiny, beautiful, funny, tragic moments in your life – how are you going to remember them all?”.</summary></entry></feed>